[
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Sheldon's favorite number?",
    "answers": ["73", "42", "64", "27"],
    "correct": "73"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Sheldon's girlfriend?",
    "answers": ["Amy Farrah Fowler", "Penny", "Bernadette", "Leslie Winkle"],
    "correct": "Amy Farrah Fowler"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What does Sheldon call his grandmother?",
    "answers": ["Meemaw", "Nana", "Granny", "Gammy"],
    "correct": "Meemaw"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Leonard's last name?",
    "answers": ["Hofstadter", "Cooper", "Wolowitz", "Koothrappali"],
    "correct": "Hofstadter"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of the comic book store owner?",
    "answers": ["Stuart", "Howard", "Raj", "Barry"],
    "correct": "Stuart"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Howard's wife?",
    "answers": ["Bernadette", "Penny", "Amy", "Leslie"],
    "correct": "Bernadette"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Which university do Sheldon and Leonard work at?",
    "answers": ["Caltech", "MIT", "Stanford", "UCLA"],
    "correct": "Caltech"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Raj's dog?",
    "answers": ["Cinnamon", "Sugar", "Pepper", "Ginger"],
    "correct": "Cinnamon"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What instrument does Leonard play?",
    "answers": ["Cello", "Piano", "Guitar", "Violin"],
    "correct": "Cello"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Sheldon's catchphrase?",
    "answers": ["Bazinga", "Eureka", "Alakazam", "Shazam"],
    "correct": "Bazinga"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Howard's mother's first name?",
    "answers": ["Debbie", "Marianne", "Linda", "Susan"],
    "correct": "Debbie"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Leonard's mother?",
    "answers": ["Beverly", "Mary", "Amy", "Leslie"],
    "correct": "Beverly"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Sheldon's IQ?",
    "answers": ["187", "160", "200", "175"],
    "correct": "187"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Where is Sheldon originally from?",
    "answers": ["Texas", "California", "New York", "Florida"],
    "correct": "Texas"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Raj's profession?",
    "answers": ["Astrophysicist", "Engineer", "Physicist", "Chemist"],
    "correct": "Astrophysicist"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What food do the guys eat every Monday night?",
    "answers": ["Thai food", "Chinese food", "Pizza", "Burgers"],
    "correct": "Thai food"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Sheldon's sister's name?",
    "answers": ["Missy", "Penny", "Mary", "Amy"],
    "correct": "Missy"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Which character is an aerospace engineer?",
    "answers": ["Howard", "Leonard", "Raj", "Sheldon"],
    "correct": "Howard"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of the building superintendent?",
    "answers": [
      "Mr. Wolowitz",
      "Mr. Hofstadter",
      "Mr. Koothrappali",
      "Mr. Koothrapali"
    ],
    "correct": "Mr. Wolowitz"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Penny's last name before she gets married?",
    "answers": ["Penny", "Hofstadter", "Cooper", "Fowler"],
    "correct": "Penny"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Sheldon's favorite childhood TV show?",
    "answers": [
      "Professor Proton",
      "Fun with Flags",
      "Science World",
      "Geek Weekly"
    ],
    "correct": "Professor Proton"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Leonard allergic to?",
    "answers": ["Lactose", "Gluten", "Peanuts", "Shellfish"],
    "correct": "Lactose"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of the actress who plays Amy Farrah Fowler?",
    "answers": [
      "Mayim Bialik",
      "Kaley Cuoco",
      "Melissa Rauch",
      "Laura Spencer"
    ],
    "correct": "Mayim Bialik"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What does Howard wear as a trademark accessory?",
    "answers": ["Turtlenecks", "Bow ties", "Suspenders", "Beanies"],
    "correct": "Turtlenecks"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Raj's full name?",
    "answers": [
      "Rajesh Koothrappali",
      "Rajesh Koothrapali",
      "Rajesh Koothapali",
      "Rajesh Koothrpali"
    ],
    "correct": "Rajesh Koothrappali"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Who is Sheldon's roommate?",
    "answers": ["Leonard", "Raj", "Howard", "Stuart"],
    "correct": "Leonard"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What university does Sheldon attend as a child prodigy?",
    "answers": ["East Texas Tech", "MIT", "Stanford", "Caltech"],
    "correct": "East Texas Tech"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Sheldon's twin sister?",
    "answers": ["Missy", "Penny", "Mary", "Amy"],
    "correct": "Missy"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Leonard's middle name?",
    "answers": ["Leakey", "Lee", "Lucas", "Louis"],
    "correct": "Leakey"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What was the name of the app Raj and Howard created?",
    "answers": [
      "The Science Exploration App",
      "The Science Experiment App",
      "The Science Innovation App",
      "The Science Explanation App"
    ],
    "correct": "The Science Explanation App"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Who is known for saying 'Soft Kitty, Warm Kitty'?",
    "answers": ["Sheldon", "Leonard", "Penny", "Amy"],
    "correct": "Sheldon"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Howard and Bernadette's first child?",
    "answers": ["Halley", "Penny", "Amy", "Sarah"],
    "correct": "Halley"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of the character that dates Sheldon?",
    "answers": ["Amy", "Penny", "Bernadette", "Leslie"],
    "correct": "Amy"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the title of the theme song for 'The Big Bang Theory'?",
    "answers": [
      "Big Bang",
      "The History of Everything",
      "The Universe",
      "Big Bang Universe"
    ],
    "correct": "The History of Everything"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Leonard and Penny's child?",
    "answers": ["Unnamed", "Halley", "Neil", "Sarah"],
    "correct": "Unnamed"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Howard's nickname for his mother?",
    "answers": ["Ma", "Mommy", "Mother", "Mama"],
    "correct": "Ma"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Who does Sheldon idolize?",
    "answers": ["Spock", "Kirk", "Picard", "Skywalker"],
    "correct": "Spock"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Sheldon's favorite spot on the couch?",
    "answers": ["Sheldon's Spot", "The Soft Spot", "The Cushion", "The Seat"],
    "correct": "Sheldon's Spot"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What did Howard go to space as?",
    "answers": ["Astronaut", "Engineer", "Scientist", "Pilot"],
    "correct": "Astronaut"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Raj's profession?",
    "answers": ["Astrophysicist", "Engineer", "Physicist", "Chemist"],
    "correct": "Astrophysicist"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Penny's job at the beginning of the series?",
    "answers": ["Waitress", "Actress", "Scientist", "Student"],
    "correct": "Waitress"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is Leonard's job?",
    "answers": [
      "Experimental Physicist",
      "Theoretical Physicist",
      "Engineer",
      "Chemist"
    ],
    "correct": "Experimental Physicist"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What is the name of Raj's sister?",
    "answers": ["Priya", "Penny", "Priyanka", "Preity"],
    "correct": "Priya"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "What does Sheldon use to determine which movie to watch?",
    "answers": [
      "Movie Algorithm",
      "Coin Toss",
      "Wheel of Fortune",
      "Random Selection"
    ],
    "correct": "Movie Algorithm"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Who does Howard impersonate often?",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Cage",
      "Al Pacino",
      "Robert De Niro",
      "Christopher Walken"
    ],
    "correct": "Nicholas Cage"
  },
  {
    "quizId": "667084b04cea098ea6038b79",
    "question": "Where does Amy work?",
    "answers": ["Caltech", "UCLA", "Stanford", "Harvard"],
    "correct": "Caltech"
  }
]
